Attention passengers:
train arriving on platform three.
Nakadori Street Shopping District
Ogikubo
Mornin', Saneatsu!
Hey...you're always
so energetic, Kazuhiko.
Man, you must really hate informatics!
Informatics...You mean computer class.
I'm just so bad at it.
When it comes to computers,
you're "Sorry-atsu"!
Shaddup!
Is Ryuta not here yet?
He's prolly late again!
Enough talking, guys. Turn your PC on.
Yeah, yeah...
Huh?
Two left
You are currently
looking at this screen
What's this?
Shinozaki-sensei!
There's something weird on my screen!
Something weird?
Two left
You are currently
looking at this screen
You mean the screen saver?
Push any button to turn it off.
Didn't even come look.
Hey, you're right.
Anyway, Sato, find your seat!
Yessir!
Mornin'.
You're late, Ryuta!
Hey, Tardy Monster!
Shaddup, you Flunking Machine!
Come on, that was a low blow!
Okay, I'm going home.
See ya!
All right.
See ya tomorrow!
I think I'll head home today, too.
Come on, you don't wanna hang out?
Today's the anniversary
of my mom's death, so...
Is your dad still living overseas?
Yeah, he just transfers me
some money from time to time.
Well, if you ever need
anything just lemme know.
We're best friends, after all.
Ryuta...
Go to hell.
All right, see ya tomorrow!
Yeah, see ya!
There it is!
Awesome!
Come on in!
Here you go!
No signal detected
Didn't we just buy this last year?
Dad
Calling
No answer...
Why's it so quiet today?
Ryuta... I should go get him.
I wonder if his parents
already left for work...
He's definitely still passed out in bed.
Can't be helped...
Ryuta!
Hey, Ryuta! What's wrong?! Are you okay?!
Ippy-hiko
Incoming Call
Hey, Saneatsu?! Thank god!
Kazuhiko! Get help!
Something's wrong with Ryuta!
Ryuta, too...
Listen to me, Saneatsu.
Ryuta's probably already dead.
You made it, Saneatsu!
I'm so glad you're safe...
What's all this about?
What the hell's going on?!
I'm Yagihashi, president of the
student council. Allow me to explain.
I'll cut to the chase. None of us
have any idea what's going on.
What the hell do you mean?!
Our families are all dead.
We're most likely the only ones
left alive from this school.
Saneatsu Narita...You saw the state
of our town on your way here, right?
We can't contact the police, the fire department, anyone.
It's reasonable to conclude they're all dead.
Dead? Everyone in town...
I woke up and found my
entire family dead, too...
Kazuhiko...
We don't know what happened, but
the fact is people all over town are dead.
The ten people here are the only ones
we've been able to contact.
The others are likely...
School Contact List
One left
Japanese citizens living in Tokyo Prefecture
Sensei?
No, that wasn't me!
This is yesterday's...
No, it's a different question.
Wait, you saw the same thing, Pres?
I saw it, too.
I did, too.
Me, too.
You mean, everyone here...
What was yesterday's question?
Two left
You are currently
looking at this screen
I think it was...
One left
Japanese citizens living in Tokyo Prefecture
It disappeared!
It's not connected to the internet.
Network signal
Disconnected
In fact, there's no internet signal at all.
Fujishiro-san...
Yes!
I have a favor to ask of you
as Student Council Officer.
Still no good....
Thanks for the meal.
So we've got no gas, but
we can use water and electricity.
The radio seems to be working.
All right, everyone. Let's all wait at home.
Go home and gather your things
to meet up again tomorrow.
But promise me you'll come back here.
For your own safety.
We'll find answers tomorrow.
Tomorrow...
I'll be taking roll call.
First-year, Class D. Saaya Fujishiro.
Second-year, Class B. Mika Kaido.
First-year, Class C. Omi Jin.
Second-year, Class A. Eren Kunashiri.
Third-year, Class F. Ryohei Sudo.
I teach the first-year information
processing class, Sotaro Shinozaki.
First-year, Class A—
Hang on! Where's the President?
The President is... dead.
He left a message for me.
What do you mean "dead"?!
He killed himself?!
At a time like this?! You gotta be kidding!
Shut your mouth!
According to the President's theory,
this was the cause.
The question displayed
on the computer screen.
The question?
The question from two days ago...
Two left
You are currently
looking at this screen
And the question from yesterday...
One left
Japanese citizens living in Tokyo Prefecture
Both were asked in a "yes" or "no" format.
None of us clicked on an answer,
but the President said...
I commute from Saitama Prefecture.
If these questions really are
the reason people are dying,
then either me or all of you will die.
That's hardly scientific!
But come to think of it...
If people who were on the "no" side
of the first question were the ones to die,
Two left
You are currently
looking at this screen
everything so far would make sense...
Then ya mean people who didn't
see the first screen are all dead?
Another question?!
Hang on, something's different!
Zero left
Test run complete
Rules will be announced tonight at 23:40
It's... not a question?
Wait a second, what do
they mean by "test run"?
Test run
Zero left
Test run complete
Rules will be announced tonight at 23:40
Either way, this means there
will be another message tonight!
So we're starting to grasp what's happening,
but my mind can't keep up!
Sensei, can you open the conference room?
We'll all be able to see if we use a projector!
You're right. Let's get set up!
Is any of this real?
Do we have everyone here?
Hey, wasn't there
another guy here yesterday?
I didn't see him during the day, either.
Oh, you mean that stuck-up guy?
Maybe he's dead.
Did anyone call him?
Actually, we can't find
the contact list...
Either way, there's no service network
anymore for calls or messages.
Phone service unavailable
You're right...
I guess we'll just have to give up
on contacting each other.
Does it matter if we can't use it?
We're the only ones alive, anyway.
We don't know that for sure.
Phone service unavailable
If only this was some terrible joke...
Zero left
Test run complete
Rules will be announced tonight at 23:40
What am I saying?! People are dying!
Congratulations. You are all alive by chance.
Nice to meet you, I'm the Emperor.
For the one million of you still alive in Tokyo,
the test run has concluded.
We will now begin the Tasuketsu (Absent Majority).
Tasuketsu
Tasuketsu...
Absent
"Absent" majority?
Tasuketsu
The rules are simple.
All of you must search for
blue postboxes or red PCs
in Designated Areas that change daily.
You
Submit a question with two possible answers.
Questions including designations of individual
people or previously featured questions
Questions with designated individuals
Previously featured questions
will not be counted.
The first applicable question
submitted will be featured.
You
1 accepted
The deadline is 23:55 PM daily.
We will follow with announcements
of the featured question from 23:58 PM.
And every day at midnight, the majority
side of the two answers will die.
The majority were the ones dying?!
If submissions are not accepted, a random
question will be selected from our library.
This has to be a sick joke!
That means, best case scenario,
half of those left will die...
Within Designated Areas, there
are also a total of 65 envelopes
Special Privilege         Privilege
that contain unique powers called
"special privileges" and "privileges".
Special Privilege         Privilege
Each person can obtain up to one of each.
Once obtained, you may not exchange
or modify your privilege.
Please use them well.
...Sounds like a bunch of magic.
Finally, when one person remains,
they will be offered the privilege
of meeting the Emperor.
The Emperor... So you'll meet us.
Now, for the announcement
of tomorrow's Designated Area.
Suginami Ward
The leader will be Fujishiro, I'll be the
assistant leader, and the officer will be Sudo.
L               AL           O
Fujishiro
Sensei
Sudo
1st place nationwide
in trial exams
It just so happens we're already in
today's Designated Area, Suginami Ward.
Let's all search for red PCs or blue postboxes
and meet back up at 23:00 PM.
Sidewalk
We're in this together.
Let's all make it out alive!
I can't believe we're doing this separately!
Idiots! You're all a bunch of idiots!
All the bodies are gone.
But my biggest question is...
Are there really a million people left?
It's way too quiet for that.
So? What's this you wanted to tell me
that's more important than our search?
Since you're our leader and
the successor to the President,
I wanted to tell you about my plan...
I'll take down the Emperor!
T-Take down?!
Making it out alive means nothing
if it means being alone.
That's why surviving the Tasuketsu
isn't my purpose, it's my means...
...to find the Emperor.
And there's no guarantee that
someone will be left in the end, anyway.
Like the Emperor said,
"When one person remains,
they'll be offered the privilege
of meeting the Emperor".
But only "when one person remains".
If it's zero against everyone, we all die.
Since it's at least possible to meet
the Emperor, they're around here somewhere.
We've just gotta find them and stop them.
But there's problems with the Tasuketsu.
The Emperor's only told us
the absolute minimal rules.
What happens if there's an equal
number of responses to a question, say?
Does it not count, do both sides die,
or will there be some kind of adjustment?
The worst part is that we don't know what questions count and don't.
Can you ask any question you want,
as long as the question
only has two responses?
What could the Emperor be thinking?
Or are they not thinking at all?
And why an "absent" majority?
There's so many mysteries.
Can I add something that's
been bothering me, too?
As of this morning, we have no gas,
internet, or phone service.
Network signal
Disconnected
Phone service unavailable
But we still have electricity,
water, and radio.
I think this could mean something.
This morning... Morning...
"Morning"?
No, I was just remembering
the morning two days ago...
It feels strange that you guys were so calm.
It was all thanks to the President.
He was the one who called us
and got us to meet up together.
After that, he forced us
to contact people one by one.
Suginami Second High School
Contact List
I was confused at first, but it's thanks
to him we were able to stay calm.
I think the President did it...
For us...
Hang on a sec...
How did the President come to Tokyo
when the trains were down
and he lived all the way out in Saitama?
How did he arrive at the school
before everyone else?
Could the President have known...
...that the Tasuketsu had already begun?!
Sa-ne-a-tsu!
Huh?
Saneatsu!
W-w-why are you calling me
by name all the sudden?!
Relax, relax...
I mean... we don't know when we're gonna die.
Might as well get close
to people in the meantime.
S-Saaya...
Great!
Anyways, I had no idea how smart you were.
I've got brains and athletic skill,
as they say in my class.
But when it comes to computers,
I'm "Sorry-atsu".
So I leave the PC stuff to you!
I'll find postboxes and the Emperor!
I'll help you find the Emperor!
Let's work together, Saneatsu!
Oh, sorry!
You can't hold my hand like that!
Let's um! Find stuff we can
take back and use!
I guess I got too close...
While we're here!
Or would that be stealing?
That reminds me... Paper!
Let's take something to write our
questions on, like receipt paper!
Privilege
Should we open it?
Let's wait until everyone's here.
Since we couldn't find a postbox, after all...
Nothing's here at the school.
It's not easy finding a laptop...
Probably better off
trying postboxes instead.
I figured someone would be here at school.
Sudo-senpai?! Where did you get that?!
Like I'll tell you!
...I found it lying on the street.
Wait, did you just?!
I knew my theory was right...
The correct answer is to kill!
That's how to stop the Tasuketsu!
Are you gonna shoot me?!
Of course I am.
I refuse.
Found you! Great, follow me!
We're going to the front entrance now!
Kazuhiko?
What's wrong?
Sudo-senpai's walking around with a gun!
Narita! Fujishiro! Sato! Get in!
Sensei!
Narita, look out!
Stop, you idiot nerd!
Fine then, you'll be first...
Wait, no!
Damn it!
I won't give up...
I've narrowed down where you are... Emperor!
I guess we can't go to school anymore.
I'm just glad you guys are safe.
Safe how?! Kaido hasn't come back
and no one found a postbox!
We're done for!
Let's keep looking!
We may still find one in time!
Sensei, could you take on
the role of Officer?
Right, sure... But promise me
you'll come back here.
Damn it!
"Find one in time," my ass!
Saneatsu, let's take a break.
I jokingly told my best friend
to "go to hell"...
Since he died, I've felt so guilty.
I promised I'd at least avenge him.
Now look at me, not accomplishing anything.
Saneatsu... Let's take a picture.
Huh?
When, if not now? Come on!
Okay, but...
Ready? Three...
Not like that!
Wow, Saaya. You're great at taking pictures.
I'm only average.
It's all about focusing on or
framing around the main shot.
My cellphone isn't even cut out
to take selfies in the first place.
I've never cared... or needed to, I guess.
I wish...
I wish we could've taken one
with the whole group.
The whole group...
Our group!
I can't believe we lost track of time...
Let's watch here. We can
meet up with the group later.
No signal detected
It's time. We will now begin
tallying the majority.
What's coming?
What could the question be?!
Male or Female
Whose idea was this?
Promise me something.
Whoever makes it out alive...
...will take down the Emperor. Promise.
Male or Female
We've passed midnight.
Nakano Ward
Emperor!
Tomorrow